welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we'll learn about the basics of
视频我们将了解以下基础知识
layers within there's a couple
里面有几层
different things to know about layers
关于层需要了解的不同事情
one is we can use layers across the top
其一是我们可以在顶部使用层
menu bar here we can create a new layer
菜单栏在这里我们可以创建一个新的层
and there's some different options for
还有一些不同的选择
layers we can delete or duplicate a
我们可以删除或复制的层
layer and then the way that we interact
层 然后是我们交互的方式
with these layers is over here towards
有了这些层 就在这里走向
the right-hand side and right now we see
右手边 现在我们看到
we have one layer called background now
我们现在有一个称为背景的层
if you're not seeing this or if it's not
如果你没有看到这个或者如果它没有
called background for example if this is
调用后台 例如 如果这是
close if we don't have a document our
如果我们没有文档 请关闭
layers appears empty because we have no
层显示为空 因为我们没有
layer because we have no project but if
层 因为我们没有项目 但如果
we open up an image maybe I'll just open
我们打开一张图片 也许我会打开
an image for a good example we'll choose
我们将选择一幅图像作为一个很好的例子
an image and we'll open it up just a
一张图片 我们将只打开一张
regular JPEG image and now we see the
常规的JPEG图像 现在我们可以看到
name of the image and it is also our
图像的名称 它也是我们的
layer we can change the name by just
层我们只需更改名称即可
double-clicking in here and we can call
在这里双击 我们就可以呼叫
this guy and so this is like the the guy
这个人 所以这就像是那个人
layer but the reason layers are nice is
层 但层很好的原因是
because let's say we wanted to draw we
因为比方说我们想画我们
want that like circle this guy well if
想要像这样把这家伙好好圈起来如果
we want if we draw the circle and then
我们希望如果我们画出圆圈 然后
later on we get doing something else we
稍后我们会做一些其他的事情
adjust the colors and we want to move
调整颜色 我们想要移动
change this circle a little bit we've
稍微改变一下这个圆圈 我们已经
learned in the past we could kind of
从过去学到的东西 我们可以
select there's different options but
选择有不同的选项 但是
really since it's all on the same layer
真的 因为它们都在同一层上
what we've done is we've drawn we've
我们所做的是我们已经画出了我们已经
changed the pixels underneath this to
将此下面的像素更改为
black they're all just black now so if
他们现在都是黑色的 所以如果
we want to move it we can grab the move
我们想要移动它 我们可以抓住移动
tool but what we're going to end up
工具 但我们最终会得到什么
doing is moving the circle and the image
所做的就是移动圆圈和图像
together and if that's not what we want
如果这不是我们想要的
to do what we could do is I'll do ctrl Z
我们可以做的是 我会按Ctrl Z键
a bunch of times
很多次
we can come over here and go layer new
我们可以到这里来 开始新的一层
layer or I can right click in this area
层或我可以在此区域中单击鼠标右键
and just go to new layer and it brings
只需转到新的层 它就会带来
up this dialog to create a new layer so
打开此对话框以创建新层 以便
I'll call this layer circle I was doing
我把我做的这个圈子叫做层圈
this earlier which is why that populated
这就是为什么这个人
with that I'll leave everything else the
有了这一点 我将把所有其他的东西
same and hit OK
相同 然后点击OK
so now I have this circle layer and it
所以现在我有了这个圈层 它
has a little white highlight around it
周围有一个白色的小高光
that's telling me that that is the layer
这告诉我那就是那一层
I'm on not the guy layer last time when
上一次我不是在男人的层面上
I drew the circle I was on the guy layer
我画了一个圆圈 我在男子组
so I'm going to click on this circle
所以我要点击这个圆圈
layer and now I'm going to go into dry
一层一层 现在我要干了
circle
圆
just like last time and now if I want to
就像上次和现在一样 如果我想
move it'll just move the circle what
移动它只会移动圆圈什么
it's really doing is moving everything
它真正要做的就是移动一切
on this layer and we could do we can
在这一层上 我们可以做到我们可以
grab like the resize at the scale tool
像在缩放工具上调整大小一样抓取
and we can scale and change the size of
我们可以扩展和改变
this circle but again what we're really
这个圈子 但又是我们真正的样子
doing is changing the scale of
正在做的事情正在改变
everything on this layer and by that I
这一层上的一切 到那一层我
mean if I if I had something else drawn
我是说 如果我画了别的东西
over here and I wanted to do let me
在这里和我想做的事情让我
point like an arrow or something well if
像箭头或其他东西一样指向如果
we go to move now it's going to move the
我们现在要搬家了它会搬家的
circle but we can't select just the
圈 但我们不能只选择
circle and move it separately without
单独圈出并移动它 而不是
moving this arrow and also this I can
移动这个箭头 还有这个 我可以
also come over here to just the layer of
也来到这里 仅仅是这一层
the guy or just the layer of the entire
这个男人 或者只是整个社会的一层
image and I can move the entire image
图像和我可以移动整个图像
around now keeping these everything else
现在把这些其他的东西都保存起来
is drawn on the other layer intact now
现在完好无损地绘制在另一层上
if I'm going to drag it right here we
如果我要把它拖到这里
see these dots these a sort of squares
看到这些点了吗 这是一种正方形
here we've looked at a little bit in the
在这里 我们已经看了一点
past this just shows that this is
过去的这只表明这是
transparency so when this image is
透明度 所以当这张图像
actually rendered out and let's just do
实际上渲染出来了 我们就这么做吧
it right now and see what it would look
现在 看看它会是什么样子
like if we go to export as and I'll call
例如 如果我们去出口 我会打电话给
it test and put it on the desktop we can
它测试并将其放在我们可以
see what this image will look like I'll
看看这张图片会是什么样子 我会
just export it so this image looks like
只需将其导出 使此图像看起来像
this now it has white up here because it
这个现在上面有白色 因为它
was transparent and it just defaulted to
是透明的 它只是缺省为
white and it cut off the bottom of that
白色的 它切断了它的底部
but it still has both these layers but
但它仍然有这两层 但
now everything is all just together it's
现在一切都在一起了
just a collection of pixels I can't edit
只是一组我不能编辑的像素
these layers I can't move this arrow or
这些层我不能移动这个箭头或者
the circle independently it's all just
独立的圈子 这一切都只是
one flattened image that's called like
一张平面化的图像 叫做Like
flattened when you do that but in here I
当你这样做的时候是扁平的 但在这里我
still can do that but I want to show you
仍然可以做到这一点 但我想向你展示
what that transparency looks like also
这种透明度也是什么样子的
over here we have these little eyes so
在这里 我们有一双小眼睛
we can turn off just this layer and keep
我们可以只关闭这一层并保持
looking at this layer maybe it's
看看这一层 也许它是
distracting us we want to just draw and
分散我们的注意力 我们只想画和
then turn this on it's still there it's
然后打开它 它还在那里 它在
not deleted or anything it's just
没有被删除或其他什么 只是
toggling whether it's viewable or not
切换它是否可见
the eye when the eyes closed or off it's
当眼睛闭上或睁开时 它是
not viewable and when it's open it is
不可见 打开时可见
viewable we can turn off the drawing
可查看我们可以关闭图形
part too and we could bring in another
也有一部分 我们可以再带一个
layer if we wanted we can right-click
如果需要 可以右键单击该层
and go new layer we can just call this
进入新的一层我们可以称之为
one whatever we want to
一个我们想要的任何东西
and now we have this different type of
现在我们有了这种不同类型的
this different layer here and maybe I'll
这个不同的层面 也许我会
do something well watch this if we grab
好好做点什么看这个如果我们抓住
the smudge tool and I try to apply
涂抹工具和我尝试应用
smudge here or we try to do the clone
涂抹在这里 否则我们就试着克隆
tool and we try to clone different parts
工具 我们尝试克隆不同的部分
nothing's happening that's because we're
什么都没发生是因为我们
referencing nothing the the layer were
这些层没有引用任何内容
on is this so if I turn off these this
这是开着的吗？所以如果我把它关掉
is what we're really seeing so we're
是我们真正看到的 所以我们
cloning but we're cloning transparency
克隆 但我们在克隆透明度
into transparency and when we grab the
变得透明 当我们抓住
smudge tool we're smudging transparency
涂抹工具我们正在涂抹透明度
and when we grab the move tool we're
当我们抓住移动工具时 我们就是
moving transparency so and that really
移动透明度真的是这样那样
is actually looks like it is moving the
实际上看起来像是在移动
the layer you can layer because the
您可以分层的层 因为
layer is the same size it has attributes
图层的大小与其具有的属性相同
too but what I want to show with that is
我也是 但我想展示的是
if we have everything turned on and
如果我们把所有的东西都打开
let's take this one and let's just fill
让我们拿着这个 我们把它填满
it with a color so that the transparency
它用一种颜色来使透明度
is not throwing us off let's fill it
不会把我们甩了让我们把它填满
with red and now it fills everything but
红色 现在它填满了一切 除了
the black still there but the picture is
黑色还在那里 但照片是
gone right now this guy image is at the
现在这个人的形象已经消失在
very bottom which is why we can't see it
非常底层 这就是为什么我们看不到它
if we left click and drag it to the
如果我们左键单击并将其拖动到
middle it's kind of above the red but
中间是红色的上面 但是
it's behind the this circle that's why
它在这个圆圈后面 这就是为什么
the circles on top but the red is behind
上面是圆圈 后面是红色
the image and if we drag this on top
如果我们把这张图片拖到上面
then we just see the image well it's
然后我们只需看到图像 这是
dragged down so we see a little bit
拖累了 所以我们看到了一点
differently but we can't see those black
不同 但我们看不到那些黑色
arrows on top let's say we grab this red
上面的箭头 假设我们抓住这个红色
layer it's just solid red and drag it on
层它只是稳定的红色并将其拖上
top well now we only see red so whatever
好的 现在我们只看到红色 所以不管怎样
is on top is what you see first and then
在上面是你首先看到的 然后
if there's any gaps or transparency like
如果有任何间隙或透明度 比如
those squares you'll see it behind that
那些正方形 你会看到它在那后面
make sense so if we were to turn this
所以如果我们把这件事
off this red we see the transparency
在红色之外 我们看到了透明
what's really there which is nothing
那里到底有什么 什么都没有
transparent unless something's in its
透明的 除非里面有东西
way and then it appears there this is a
然后看起来这是一个
basic introduction there's a lot more
基本介绍还有更多内容
that we're gonna get into with layers
我们将以层次分明的方式
but go ahead and play with these for now
不过 现在先来玩这些吧
toggling viewing it and then toggling
切换查看 然后切换
when you're selected on the layer and
当您在层上被选中并且
just know when you have a certain tool
只要知道什么时候你有一个特定的工具
selected like move make sure that you're
选择Like Move确保您是
moving the layer you can hover over and
移动您可以悬停在上面的层并
move the layer and not the selection
移动层而不是选区
because you can also move the selection
因为您还可以移动选定内容
like we learned about previously
就像我们之前了解到的
and that just moves what is selected it
这只会移动它所选择的内容
doesn't really move the lair this one
这一次不会真的移动老巢
you can either pick a lair to move so
你可以选择一个巢穴来搬家
whatever lair you click on will move or
你点击的任何巢穴都会移动或
if you say move active layer it'll move
如果你说移动活动层 它就会移动
whatever layer is selected but always
选定的任何层 但始终
whenever you're using like a drawing
当你像画一样使用的时候
tool or most of the tools over here
工具或大多数工具都在这里
it'll usually only apply to whatever
它通常只适用于
layer has this little white highlight
层有这个白色的小高光
around it whichever one you're selected
在它周围 无论你选择了哪一个
on well that's the basic layers
好的 这是基本的层次
hopefully I haven't confused you any
希望我没有把你搞糊涂
more with that one go ahead and leave
再来一张 走吧 走吧
your questions and comments below if you
您的问题和评论如下 如果您
have any and take a little time to play
有任何 花一点时间玩
with layers because it's a very
因为它是一个非常
fundamental part of and
和的基本部分
understanding layers is going to help
理解图层将有助于
you be able to go a lot farther in
你就能走得更远
thanks for watching catch you in the
感谢收看《抓住你》
next video
下一个视频